jobstreet.co.th 2016-04-07

# Privacy Policy | jobsDB Thailand

jobsDB Thailand respects the privacy of the personal information and data of its users and will ensure compliance by its staff to the strictest standards of security and confidentiality in respect of all personal information and data submitted by users via the Site and jobsDB Thailand will not, subject to the terms herein, release such information to anyone without the prior consent of the relevant user(s) of the Site (whether registered or not) (“ **User(s)** ”).

Users are strongly recommended to read this privacy statement ( **“Privacy Statement”** ) carefully to have an understanding of jobsDB Thailand’s policy and practices with regard to the treatment of personal information and data provided by Users on the Site. This Privacy Statement is applicable to both registered and unregistered Users, and the terms herein may be updated, revised, varied and/or amended from time to time as jobsDB Thailand may deem necessary and/or appropriate.

By registering for or using the services/Site, or by clicking the ‘Register’ button, User:

(a) | 

consent to jobsDB Thailand and/or jobsDB Thailand’s group companies collecting, using, disclosing and/or processing User’s personal data for the purposes as described below;  
  
---|---  
(b) | 

consent to jobsDB Thailand and/or jobsDB Thailand’s group companies disclosing Users’ personal data to jobsDB Thailand’s and/or jobsDB Thailand’s group companies’ third party service providers or agents (whether within or outside Thailand) for the purposes as described below.  
  
If Users have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Statement, they should contact the Customer Support Executive of jobsDB Thailand’s Customer Service Department, whose contact details are set out under the section headed “ **Enquiries** ” below.

In this Privacy Statement, the following terms shall have the respective meanings specified below unless the context otherwise requires:

“ **Advertiser(s)** ” means user who places a job advertisement or promotes any job related activities via the Site.   
“ **jobsDB** ” means Jobs DB Inc.   
“ **jobsDB Group** ” means Jobs DB Hong Kong Limited, Jobs DB Singapore Pte Ltd, Jobs DB Philippines Inc, Jobs DB Recruitment (Thailand) Limited and PT Jobs DB Indonesia.   
“ **jobsDB Thailand** ” means Jobs DB Recruitment (Thailand) Limited.   
“ **Job Seeker(s)** ” means users seeking employment.   
“ **Register User(s)** ” means Users who register on the Site to obtain services offered by jobsDB. Unless the context provides otherwise, references in this Privacy Statement to “users” or “you” include references to generic users and Registered Users.   
“ **Site** ” means any website, job portal or mobile application owned and operated by jobsDB and its affiliates/subsidiaries. 

**Purpose of Collection and Use of Personal Data**

In the course of using the Site, Users may disclose or be asked to provide personal information and/or data. In order to have the benefit of and enjoy various services offered by the Site, it may be necessary for Users to provide jobsDB Thailand with their personal information and/or data. Although Users are not obliged to provide the information and/or data as requested on the Site, jobsDB Thailand will not be able to render certain services on the Site in the event that Users fail to do so.

jobsDB Thailand’s purposes for collecting and using the information and data on the Site include but are not limited to the following:

(a) | for the daily operation of the services provided to Users;  
---|---  
(b) | 

to assist Job Seekers to find appropriate employment with Employers and to assist Employers to assess the suitability of candidates for job vacancy for a wide spectrum of jobs and industries;  
  
(c) | 

to provide Users with various services offered by the Site and newsletters, job openings and promotional and marketing materials (for further details, please refer to section headed “ **Subscription of Newsletter/Promotional Materials/Marketing Materials** ” below);  
  
(d) | 

to handle and follow up on enquiries, requests and complaints from Users;  
  
(e) | 

to contact Users regarding administrative notices and communications relevant to his/her use of the Site and to respond to Users’ inquiries or requests;  
  
(f) | 

to assist jobsDB Thailand with developments for future marketing and promoting purposes or other internal purposes;  
  
(g) | 

to verify the identity of Users who have posted advertisements, materials, representations, messages, views or comments or such other information (collectively “ **Information** ”) on the Site;  
  
(h) | 

to identify Users who have viewed the Information posted on the Site;  
  
(i) | 

to allow Users to enjoy their benefits as members of the Site by enrolling for special events and promotions hosted by jobsDB Thailand and or its affiliates and or partner company;  
  
(j) | 

to identify Users who have enjoyed their benefits as members of the Site by receiving and using marketing promotional materials;  
  
(k) | 

to facilitate jobsDB Thailand and/or its affiliates to use the Users’ personal data for the purposes relating to the provision of services offered by jobsDB Thailand and marketing services and/or special event of jobsDB Thailand and/or its affiliates;  
  
(l) | 

to obtain statistics about Users to analyze usage of the Site in order to help its further development for internal use; and  
  
(m) | 

for purposes other than the above mentioned which are related to jobsDB Thailand’s and/or its affiliates’ provision of their product and/or services as jobsDB Thailand may deem fit.  
  
If a User is under the age of 20, jobsDB Thailand would strongly recommend him/her to seek prior consent from a person with parental responsibility for him/her, e.g. parent or guardian, who may contact the responsible Customer Support Executive whose contact details are set out under the section headed “ **Enquiries** ” for registering the User as member of the Site.

jobsDB Thailand strives to only collect personal data which are necessary and adequate but not excessive in relation to the purposes set out hereinabove.

If jobsDB Thailand requires the use of your personal data for a purpose other than those set out hereinabove, we will request your prescribed consent to the same. If you are a minor, the prescribed consent should be given by your parent or guardian.

**Collection of Personal Data**  

jobsDB Thailand may collect personal information and/or data about a User such as his/her name, log-in ID and password, address, email address, phone number, age, gender, date of birth, country of residence, nationality, education level and work experience that is/are not otherwise publicly available. Occasionally, jobsDB Thailand may also collect additional personal information and/or data from a User in connection with contests, surveys, or special offers.

Only duly authorized staff of jobsDB Thailand will be permitted to access Users’ personal information and data, and jobsDB Thailand shall not release such personal information and data to any third parties save and except for the circumstances listed out under the section entitled “ **Disclosure or Transfer of Data** ”.

**Disclosure or Transfer of Data**  

jobsDB Thailand agrees to take all practicable steps to keep all personal information and data of Users confidential and/or undisclosed, subject to the following.

Generally speaking, jobsDB Thailand will only disclose and/or transfer Users’ personal information and/or data to jobsDB Thailand’s personnel and staff for the purpose of providing services to Users and corporate clients of jobsDB Thailand who have made specific requests for such information and/or data with Users’ prior consent. However, jobsDB Thailand may disclose and/or transfer such information and/or data to third parties under the following circumstances:

(a) | where the information and/or data is disclosed and/or transferred to any third party suppliers or external service providers who have been duly authorized by jobsDB Thailand to use such information and/or data and who will facilitate the services on the Site, under a duty of confidentiality;  
---|---  
(b) | 

where the information and/or data is disclosed and/or transferred to any agents, affiliates or associates of jobsDB Thailand who have been duly authorized by jobsDB Thailand to use such information and/or data;  
  
(c) | 

where permitted under the “ **[Terms and Conditions](http://th.jobsdb.com/en-th/pages/terms/terms-conditions)** ” including the “ **[Talent Search Terms and Conditions](http://th.jobsdb.com/en-th/pages/terms/talent-search-offer-terms)** ” (see the Profiles Section below);

;  
(d) | 

where jobsDB Thailand needs to protect and defend its rights and property;  
  
(e) | 

where jobsDB Thailand considers necessary to do so in order to comply with the applicable laws and regulations, including without limitation compliance with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on the Site;  
  
(f) | 

where jobsDB Thailand deems necessary in order to deliver the products and services that we offer and cultivate a positive user experience; and  
  
(g) | 

where jobsDB Thailand deems necessary in order to maintain and improve the services on the Site.  
  
Personal data collected via the Site may be transferred, stored and processed in any country in which jobsDB Thailand or any member of the jobsDB Group operates. By using the Site, Users are deemed to have agreed to, consented to and authorized jobsDB Thailand to disclose and/or transfer their personal information and data under the circumstances stated above, as well as to any transfer of information (including the Information) outside of the Users’ country.

**jobsDB Profile**

jobsDB provides all Registered Users with the option of creating a personal jobsDB Profile (“ **jobsDB Profile** ”). A jobsDB Profile can include a resume, employment and educational history, contact details, salary expectations, and preferred job classifications and locations. Advertisers who are approved by jobsDB are able to search jobsDB’s Profile database to find and contact relevant candidates. jobsDB provides Registered Users with a number of privacy options in relation to the access granted by jobsDB to Advertisers in respect of their jobsDB Profiles and Registered Users can elect how much of their jobsDB profile they wish to share (if any) with Advertisers based on the following privacy settings:

  * **STANDARD**

If you set your jobsDB Profile to standard, your Profile, except for your resume and contact details, can be seen by Advertisers searching jobsDB’s Profile database, and if an Advertiser wishes to purchase access to your jobsDB Profile, your full jobsDB Profile including your resume and contact details will be emailed immediately to the relevant Advertiser. Advertisers may also elect to send you a copy of the job opportunity for which they are recruiting, (by using the “invitations to apply for jobs” function).

  * **LIMITED**

If you set your jobsDB Profile to limited, your Profile, except for your resume and contact details, can be seen by Advertisers searching jobsDB’s Profile database and Advertisers may elect to send you a copy of the job opportunity for which they are recruiting, (by using the “invitations to apply for jobs” function). However, due to your privacy setting, Advertisers cannot purchase access to your jobsDB profile.

  * **HIDDEN**

If you set your jobsDB Profile to hidden, your Profile, is completely hidden (thereby preventing Advertisers from viewing your jobsDB Profile). Your jobsDB Profile will be stored in the ‘Profile’ area of the Site and you may alter the privacy settings at any time. Advertisers cannot purchase your profile or send you job opportunities.

Advertisers who use the invitations to apply for jobs function will only receive access to your contact information if you respond directly to the job invitation sent to you.

Where your profile has been bought by an Advertiser, you have replied to a job invitation sent by an Advertiser or you have applied for jobs directly on the Site using your profile, that Advertiser will have access to your up-to-date profile, including your contact details (as updated by you from time to time) for a period expiring two years from the date your profile was purchased, or date the Job Ad you responded was posted (as the case may be) (maximum of 24 months) (a “ **Participating Advertiser** ”). If however during the period that a Participating Advertiser has access to your updated profile, you subsequently change you profile setting to Hidden, whilst other Advertisers will no longer be able to see your profile, however, Participating Advertisers will retain the ability to access your profile (including your name), but will no longer be able to see your email address, contact phone number and work history.

Additionally, to protect your privacy, all data stored by jobsDB on an advertiser’s behalf in the advertiser’s Recruitment Centre (including data about you that the advertiser may have) will be deleted after a 2 year period.

All information provided when creating a jobsDB Profile (including your name, resume, email address, telephone numbers, employment and educational history) may be used by jobsDB for the purpose of improving placement opportunities for you or for tailoring specific products to you.

Where you create a jobsDB Profile on jobs DB Thailand Site and select a privacy setting of Standard or Limited, you consent to your profile being viewed and/or accessed by Advertisers using the websites of any member of the jobsDB Group, which may result in the transfer of your personal data from Thailand to the other countries in which the other members of the jobsDB Group operate.

Registered Users can modify their jobsDB Profile, their resume or modify the privacy options in relation to their jobsDB Profile at any time, by going to the Profile area of the Site.

You may also elect to clear your jobsDB Profile altogether. Cleared jobsDB Profiles may still however be stored by jobsDB in testing or backup systems for a period of time. jobsDB reserves the right to disable or clear a jobsDB Profile at any time at its sole discretion.

Advertisers that place job ads on jobsDB, and that purchase jobsDB Profiles are asked by jobsDB to comply with all relevant laws and obligations relating to the use and disclosure of personal information. The use of your information (personal or otherwise) by these Advertisers is not within the control of jobsDB and we cannot accept responsibility for the conduct of these companies.

**Subscription of Newsletters/Promotional Materials/Marketing Materials  **

jobsDB Thailand and its affiliates may from time to time send to members and Users of the Site newsletters, information on job openings, and marketing materials based on the personal information and data that they have provided to jobsDB Thailand. jobsDB Thailand may use Users’ data in direct marketing and jobsDB Thailand requires the Users’ consent (which includes an indication of no objection) for that purpose. In this connection, please note that:

(a) | 

the name, log-in ID and password, contact details, age, gender, date of birth, country of residence, nationality, education level and work experience of Users held by jobsDB Thailand from time to time may be used by jobsDB Thailand and/or its authorized personnel or staff in direct marketing;  
  
---|---  
(b) | 

the following classes of services, products and subjects may be marketed:

| i. | travelling related products and services;  
---|---  
ii. | job-hunting and agencies services offered other than by jobsDB Thailand;  
iii. | various courses and programs for Users seeking jobs and career opportunities;  
iv. | special events hosted by jobsDB Thailand and its affiliates for members and Users, including but not limited to courses, workshops, and competitions;  
v. | reward, loyalty or privilege programs and related products and services;  
vi. | special offers including coupons, discounts, group purchase offers and promotional campaigns;  
vii. | products and services offered by jobsDB Thailand’s affiliates and advertisers (the names of such affiliates and advertisers can be found in the application form(s) for the relevant products and services, as the case may be);  
viii. | donations and contributions for charitable and/or non-profit making purposes;  
(c) | 

the above products, services and subjects may be provided or (in the case of donations and contributions) solicited by jobsDB Thailand and/or;

| i. | jobsDB Thailand’s affiliates;  
---|---  
ii. | third party service providers providing the products, services and subjects listed in paragraph (b) above; and  
iii. | charitable or non-profit making organizations;  
(d) | 

in addition to marketing the above services, products, and subject itself, jobsDB Thailand also intends to provide the data described in paragraph (a) above to all or any of the persons described in paragraph (c) above for use by them in marketing those services, products and subjects, and jobsDB Thailand requires the Users’ written consent (which includes an indication of no objection) for that purpose; and  
  
(e) | 

jobsDB Thailand may receive money or other property in return for providing the data to the other persons in paragraph (d) above and, when requesting the Users’ written consent as described in paragraph (d) above, jobsDB Thailand will inform Users if jobsDB Thailand receives any money or other property in return for providing the data to other persons.  
  
In this regard, Users may choose to sign up or unsubscribe for such materials by logging into the registration or Users’ account maintenance webpage, or clicking on the automatic link appearing in each newsletter/message, or contact the Customer Support Executive of jobsDB Thailand, whose contact details are set out under the section headed “ **Enquiries** ”.

**Access to or request for correction of data**  

Any User is entitled to request access to or make amendments to his/her own personal information and data kept with jobsDB Thailand by contacting the Customer Support Executive of jobsDB Thailand’s Customer Service Department at whose contact details are set out under the section headed “ **Enquiries** ”. Subject to the paragraph below, User may alternatively edit, amend or delete his/her personal information and data at any time by logging into the “ **My jobsDB** section of the Site.

In the event that a User wishes to access or amend his/her personal information and data, jobsDB Thailand may request him/her to provide personal details in order to verify and confirm his/her identity. Identity card number or passport number or company registration number cannot be amended unless such data is proved to be inaccurate. jobsDB Thailand is required to respond to User’s requests within 40 days of his/her request and will endeavor to do so wherever possible, but jobsDB Thailand reserves the rights to charge the User a reasonable fee for doing so.

**Cookies and Log Files**  

jobsDB Thailand does not collect any personally identifiable information from any Users whilst they visit and browse the Site. When Users access the Site, jobsDB Thailand records their visits only and does not collect their personal information or data. The Site’s server software will also record the domain name, server, address and track the pages Users visit and store such information in “cookies”, and gather and store information like internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data in log files. All these are done without the Users being aware that they are occurring.

Users can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but Users can modify their individual browser settings to decline cookies if they prefer. However, Users should note that disabling cookies on their browser may prevent them from taking full advantage of the Site.

jobsDB Thailand does not link the information and data automatically collected in the above manner to any personally identifiable information. jobsDB Thailand generally uses such automatically collected information and data to estimate the audience size of the Site, gauge the popularity of various parts of the Site, track Users’ movements and number of entries in jobsDB Thailand’s promotional activities and special events, measure Users’ traffic patterns and administer the Site. Such automatically collected information and data will not be disclosed save and except in accordance with the section entitled “ **Disclosure or Transfer of Data** ”.

In addition, our third party advertising companies may place cookies on some of the pages Users visit on the Site. These cookies are designed to collect non-personally identifiable information in order to analyze Users’ interests and searches on our Site to help deliver more relevant advertisements when Users visit our Site and other websites. The non-personally identifiable information collected by these cookies may be shared with other third parties for purpose of managing and targeting advertisements and for market research analysis.

**Links to Other Websites  **

The Site may provide links to other websites which are not owned or controlled by jobsDB, jobsDB Thailand or its affiliates. Personal information and data from Users may be collected on these other websites when Users visit such websites and make use of the services provided therein. Where and when Users decide to click on any advertisement or hyperlink on the Site which grants Users access to another website, the protection of Users’ personal information and data which are deemed to be private and confidential may be exposed in these other websites.

Non-registered Users who gain access to the Site via their accounts in online social networking tools (including but not limited to Facebook, Twitter and Sina Weibo) are deemed to have consented to the terms of this Privacy Statement, and such Users’ personal data which they have provided to those networking tools may be obtained by jobsDB Thailand and be used by jobsDB Thailand and its authorized persons in and outside of the User’s country for the purpose of providing services and marketing materials to the Users. jobsDB Thailand and its authorized personnel may gain access and use the personal data of such Users so obtained, subject to the other provisions of this Privacy Statement.

This Privacy Statement is only applicable to the Site. Users are reminded that this Privacy Statement grants no protection to Users’ personal information and data that may be exposed on websites other than the Site, and jobsDB Thailand is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other websites. Users are strongly recommended to refer to the privacy policies of such other websites before using those websites.

**Testimonials  **

jobsDB Thailand posts Users’ testimonials on the Site, which may contain personally identifiable information such as the Users’ names. jobsDB Thailand does obtain the Users’ consent prior to posting the testimonials to post their names along with their testimonials.

**Security  **

The security of Users’ personal information and data is important to jobsDB Thailand. jobsDB Thailand will always strive to ensure that Users’ personal information and data will be protected against unauthorized access. jobsDB Thailand has implemented appropriate electronic and managerial measures in order to safeguard, protect and secure Users’ personal information and data.

All personal information and data provided by Users are only accessible by the authorized personnel of jobsDB Thailand or its authorized third parties, and such personnel shall be instructed to observe the terms of this Privacy Statement when accessing such personal information and data. Users may rest assured that their personal information and data will only be kept for as long as is necessary to fulfill the purpose for which it is collected. Registered User should safeguard his/her unique Username and Password by keeping it secret and confidential and never share these details with anyone.

jobsDB Thailand uses a third party service provider to facilitate the electronic payment transactions on the Site.

jobsDB Thailand follows generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information and data submitted by Users to the Site, both during transmission and once jobsDB Thailand receives it. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while jobsDB Thailand strives to protect Users’ personal information and data against unauthorized access, jobsDB Thailand cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**Retention of Personal Data  **

Once jobsDB Thailand has obtained a User’s personal information and/or data, it will be maintained securely in jobsDB Thailand’s system for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes for which the data was collected as set out under the section headed “ **Purpose of Collection of Personal Data** ”. Once registered, Users may terminate his/her membership of the Site by contacting the Customer Service Assistant of jobsDB Thailand’s Customer Service Department whose contact details are set out under the section headed “ **Enquiries** ”. jobsDB Thailand may retain User’s personal information even after User has closed his/her account if retention is reasonably necessary to comply with our legal obligations, meet regulatory requirements, resolve disputes between Users, prevent fraud and abuse, or enforce this Privacy Statement and the **[Terms and Conditions](https://th.jobsdb.com/en-th/pages/terms/terms-conditions)**. 

**Changes in this Privacy Statement  **

jobsDB Thailand reserves the right to update, revise, modify or amend this Privacy Statement at any time as jobsDB Thailand deems necessary, so Users are strongly advised to review this Privacy Statement frequently. If jobsDB Thailand decides to update, revise, modify or amend this Privacy Statement, jobsDB Thailand will post those changes to this webpage and/or other places as jobsDB Thailand deems appropriate, so that Users would be aware of what information jobsDB Thailand collects, how jobsDB Thailand uses it, and under what circumstances, if any, jobsDB Thailand discloses it.

If jobsDB Thailand makes material changes to this Privacy Statement, jobsDB Thailand will notify Users on this webpage, by email, or by means of a notice on the home page of jobsDB Thailand. Such changes to this Privacy Statement shall apply from the time that jobsDB Thailand posts the same on this webpage. Users’ continued use of the Site and services on the Site shall constitute acceptance of the changes to this Privacy Statement.

**Language**

This Privacy Statement is made and agreed in English which shall be the governing language. As required by the prevailing laws and regulations, this Privacy Statement may be translated into other language. In the event of any inconsistency between the English language and the other language versions, the English language version shall prevail of such inconsistency and such other language version shall be amended accordingly to reflect the meaning of the English version. Users hereby undertake that they have read this Privacy Statement and understand its English contents.

**Enquiries**

Should you have any enquiries relating to this Privacy Statement, please email at cs@jobsdb.co.th, telephone at (662) 667 0700 or write to us at the following address:

jobsDB Thailand  
1 Empire Tower III, 26th Floor, Unit 2607-2608,   
South Sathorn Road, Yannawa, Sathorn  
Bangkok 10120
